gowholesale.com 2017-06-29

# Privacy Policy | Liquidity Services

Liquidity Services, Inc., owner and operator of the websites, [www.truckcenter.com](http://www.truckcenter.com/), [www.irondirect.com](http://www.irondirect.com/), www.liquidityservices.com, [www.networkintl.com](http://www.networkintl.com/), [www.go-dove.com](http://www.go-dove.com/), [www.govliquidation.com](http://www.govliquidation.com/), [www.liquidation.com](http://www.liquidation.com/), [www.govdeals.com](http://www.govdeals.com/), [www.auctiondeals.com](http://www.auctiondeals.com/), [http://international.go-dove.com](http://international.go-dove.com/), [www.secondipity.com](http://www.secondipity.com/), and [www.unclesamsretailoutlet.com](http://www.unclesamsretailoutlet.com/) (each a “ **Website** ” and collectively the “ **Websites** ”) through its various subsidiaries (collectively, “ **Liquidity Services** ” or “ **we** ”), wants you to know that we take your privacy seriously. Because we do, our Website Privacy Policy states what information we collect, how that information is collected (whether it is by us, a vendor working for us, or some other means), for what purposes we collect information, how that information is used, and under what circumstances that information would be released. We want you to know when you have a choice regarding the collection or dissemination of any personal information, and how you can exercise your options. Our Website Privacy Policy will also explain what steps we take to secure your private information and what steps you should take to safeguard that information. Finally, our Website Privacy Policy will tell you how to correct any inaccurate information, and who you can contact regarding questions about our Website Privacy Policy.

## Consent to Collect Personal Data

By registering on a Website, by participating in an auction or sales event on a Website, by using a Website for any purpose, or by entering into a transaction with us, you consent to our Website Privacy Policy, and the collection of personal information as outlined herein. We will collect only the information that is necessary to provide the services offered via our Website, to comply with our legal obligations, to facilitate transactions with you, and to gather information about general Website traffic on our various Websites, and no additional information other than is necessary will be requested of you without first obtaining your consent to the collection and use of such additional information.

## What Information Does Do We Collect?

### Information We Collect When You Register for an Account on Our Website

When you register for an account with us through any of our Websites, we may collect information from you such as:

  * Your name
  * Your telephone number
  * Your email address
  * Your address (including, city, state, postal code, and country)
  * Business name (if applicable)
  * Number of employees (if applicable)
  * VAT / tax number
  * Customer information, including the password chosen by you to access your account

We may request additional information from you depending on certain transaction, contractual or regulatory requirements.  We will notify you of what information we need, and how it will be used.  This information is used to contact you to answer you your questions about us and to complete auctions, confirm purchases and conclude other transactions you have initiated with or through us. We may provide other Website users, our vendors, our service providers and partners with information on a winning bid or to confirm a purchase and sale.  We will also send you information regarding upcoming sales events, unique property offerings, and special announcements. If you choose, we will include information about specific property offerings you designate when you register for an account with us.  We may use information to enhance or develop features, products and services.

### Information We Collect from Persons Who Access Websites

We also collect information about your computer when you click on any of our Websites. We log your IP address, browser type, access times, and referring site to help diagnose potential problems with our server, and to administer our Websites. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information.

Our Websites use cookies to keep track of your user account. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your username so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit one of our Websites, and for other purposes. For our site to function properly, you must have cookies enabled.

### Transfers of Personal Information

Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any country where we or our affiliates or approved partners have facilities or operations, and by using our Websites, you consent to the transfer, processing, and storage of your information outside of your country.

### Cookies Policy

Cookies are small text files stored by your device when you access most of our Websites on the internet. We will use two types of cookies:

  * Session cookies - these expire when you close your browser and leave your computer.
  * Persistent cookies - these are stored in the longer term on your computer. They are normally used to make sure the site remembers your preferences.

We use cookies to make it easier to use and to support the provision of information and functionality to you. Cookies also provide us with information about how our Websites are used so we can keep them as up to date, relevant and error free as possible. Further information about the cookies in use on our Websites is set out below.  By using our Websites, you agree to our using cookies. Certain cookies may be set the moment you visit any Website. You can manage the cookies we use on our Websites through your browser settings. For more information about how to do this, and about cookies, you can visit www.allaboutcookies.org.

 Preventing cookies is likely to impact the functionality or performance of our Websites, or prevent you from using certain services provided through them. If you prevent cookies, we cannot guarantee access to the services provided through our Websites or be sure how our Websites will perform during your visit. Preventing cookies will also affect our ability to update our Websites to cater to your user preferences and improve its performance.

## Notice to California Residents

Under California Civil Code §§ 1798.80-1798.85 and California Business and Professions Code §§ 22575 – 22579, California residents are entitled to the following rights pertaining to protecting their personal information. Residents have the right to reasonable security of their personal information by us, and to destruction of any personal information that is no longer to be retained by the company via shredding, erasing or otherwise modifying the personal information in the records to make them indecipherable. Residents may expect that a business that discloses personal information about a California resident under a contract with a nonaffiliated third party shall require by contract that the third party implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information, to protect the personal information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure. Residents have a right to timely notification by us if we learn of an unauthorized disclosure or acquisition of your personal information. Residents have the right to be informed by our customer relations staff of how they can inquire about our privacy practices or compliance with the above-referenced California laws. Residents have the right to be provided contact information for inquiring about the company's privacy practices at every location in California where we do business. Residents have a right to a response to any inquiry regarding our privacy practices or compliance with California law within 30 days of receipt of the inquiry by us. We may not request you waive any of your rights under the above-referenced California laws.

## Liquidityservices.com Facebook Application

We do not include functionality that proxies, requests, or collects Facebook usernames or passwords. We do not collect data on your Facebook friends and will not use that data to customize your experience or conduct promotional activities. We will collect your basic account information when you connect with our application. For all other data obtained through the Facebook API, we will obtain explicit consent from you before using it for any purpose other than displaying it back to you on our application. We will not directly or indirectly transfer any data you receive from Facebook, including user data or Facebook User IDs, to (or use such data in connection with) any ad network, ad exchange, data broker, or other advertising or monetization related toolset, even if you consent to such transfer or use. We will not use Facebook User IDs for any purpose outside of our application. We will not sell any data. We will delete all data we receive from Facebook about a user if the user asks us to do so. We will not include data you receive from Facebook about a user in any advertising creative, even if a user consents to such use. Should you visit our Websites from Facebook, Google may add a cookie to track your visit to our Websites. We only use this information for statistical analysis. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better experience on our Websites by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie does not give us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you share with us. You can accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer.

## How Do We Collect Information About You?

Most of the information we collect about you is information voluntarily provided by you when you contact us or submit information to us, such as a registration, bid submission, purchase, resume, investor inquiry, end-use-certificate, or other communication. Other information is available to us when you click on any Website, and is collected electronically via our web engine.

## Why Do We Collect Personal Information?

We collect personal information to establish a business relationship with you, consummate a transaction with you or respond to an inquiry by you.

## How Do We Use the Information We Collect?

Information collected by us is used to communicate with you. We use the information provided by you to communicate with you regarding your specific inquiries. We do not sell customer information to third parties. We will not release your personal information to any third party without your consent, unless we are required to by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with an official investigation by a law enforcement organization.

We may provide transaction-related information to government or private auditors to inspect or validate our business practices, accounting records, or financial reports. Any release of information for such a purpose will be done under standard confidentiality restrictions.

Before we alter the reason for using any personal information you have provided to us, we will notify you of our intended change in use of that information and obtain your consent prior to using your personal information in a new way.

## Choice / Opt-Out / Deletion

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-in to receiving Buyer Alert emails from us at the point where we request information about you, and the user may contact us and request to have their information removed from the database or change their preferences via the Website’s preference center. For more information on how to change your preferences regarding buyer alert emails from a specific Website, please review the Help section of that Website or contact its dedicated Buyer Relations team.

## What Steps Do We Take to Secure Your Personal Information?

Employees having access to personal information must undergo data privacy training and are monitored by management to ensure that adequate safeguards are used to protect the private information of our customers. Our Websites have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Our Websites use SSL (secure sockets layer) encryption for all sensitive data transmitted over the Internet. This includes customers adding data to the web site, and employees transmitting data off the Website. No information, including the passwords that would give access to sensitive information, ever flows over the Internet un-encrypted

## Return of Personal Information

A user may request we discontinue the use of that person's personal information. If you would like to know what information we have collected, would like any information purged, or would like for us to discontinue using personal information, please contact our Privacy Officer at privacy@liquidityservices.com. The return of certain personal information by us may prevent you from accessing all or certain portions of our Websites, and we will endeavor to communicate to you the extent to which your request will affect your use of our Websites prior to complying with your request.

## How Can I Protect My Personal Information?

Never send credit card information via email. Do not release information about your account to anyone who is not authorized by you to transact business with us on your behalf. Do not tell your password to anyone. We will never ask you for your password to verify your identity.

## How Can I Contact You About My Personal Information?

If you believe that your personal information has been improperly released by us to a third party or if you have questions about how we collect, store, use, or destroy your personal information, you may contact us at the email address, telephone number, fax number, or mailing address listed below. When contacting us about your personal information, please do not include your account password, credit card number, date of birth, driver license number, or social security number in any email to us.

You can always change personal information such as your address, email address, phone, or fax number through the Profiles section of My Account on the Website. Credit card information can be changed when you bid in a sales event.

If you experience difficulty in correcting personal information or have questions regarding our Website Privacy Policy, please contact one of our customer service centers at the contact information on our Websites, or reach us by mail at:  
General Counsel  
Liquidity Services  
1920 L Street, NW, Sixth Floor  
Washington, DC 20036.

If you wish to file a complaint about our collection, use, disclosure, or protection of your personal information or if you have specific questions about our policies or practices regarding collection, retention, use, or disclosure of personal information, please contact us at [privacy@liquidityservices.com](mailto:privacy@liquidityservices.com).

**Liquidity Services  
1920 L Street, NW, Sixth Floor, Washington, DC 20036  
Tel. (202) 467-6868** **(202) 467-6868; Fax (202) 467-5475**

Revised December 12, 2016
